hey everybody welcome to this a2 English
listening practice video you can use
this video to train your listening and
comprehension as I speak you ready
so today I'm going to talk about travel
traveling is one of the funnest
activities
I've always loved traveling when I was
young my family and I traveled to Hawaii
many times in case you don't know much
about Hawaii it's an island in the
middle of the Pacific Ocean and it's
also one of the 50 states of the US I've
been there about six or seven times I
don't remember how many exactly it's
definitely one of my favorite places in
the world Hawaii has plenty of really
beautiful beaches and the lifestyle
there is slow and calm but even though
Hawaii is one of my favourite places to
travel to in general I prefer the
countryside the forests or the mountains
more than the beach so I love taking
camping trips and road trips I've taken
a few different road trips through the
US before and I just recently took a
road trip through the tuscany region of
italy it was one of the most incredible
experiences I've ever had if you ever
get the chance to go to Italy I highly
recommend you to rent a car and drive
through Tuscany trust me you won't be
disappointed speaking of Europe I also
took a backpacking trip through Portugal
in Spain a few years ago it was my first
time backpacking and it wasn't easy we
spent a lot of time walking and taking
buses and trains and the whole time we
had these big backpacks on her backs we
stayed in some pretty low quality
hostels and thus we had some bad
experiences the worst thing that
happened to me was that I was bitten by
bedbugs when I was in Madrid I don't
know if you've ever been bitten by
bedbugs before but it's not a fun
experience and for me it was worse
because I have really sensitive skin so
I didn't just have little red spots on
my skin I had big swole
sores all over my arms so if you plan on
staying in hostels when you travel you
should definitely read the online
reviews first sometimes it's better to
pay a little more money to stay in a
better place some people only like
staying in hotels and other people
really like air B&B ease and lately I've
been staying at air B&B ease no matter
where I travel it's definitely better
than staying in hostels in my opinion
another aspect of travel that's really
important is the flight this is probably
the worst part about traveling actually
it is the worst part definitely I've
been pretty lucky because I haven't had
any really bad flights but I have had
experiences with long delays and
canceled flights which can really ruin
your trip there were two times when I
had to spend the night at the airport
which was terrible I hope you guys don't
ever have that experience so overall
there are good and bad things about
traveling but I think we can all agree
that it's nice to travel once in a while
okay that's all for today leave a
comment and tell me your favorite place
that you've traveled to I'll see you
next video